

Igor Đukić

Software developer and architect



+381 64 4469861

Details

Vojvode Dobrnjca 28, Belgrade, 11000 Serbia

igordjukic0@gmail.com

igordjukic.com

Profile

I'm a software developer and architect based in Serbia. During 6+ years in software industry I was working on many different projects and used many different technologies.

I tend to work on all aspects of development, from designing, implementing, deploying, running, testing... I have strong affection for Unit Testing, Integration testing and process automation.

I'm very detailed, focused, with strong affection to clean and tested code.

Employment History

Feb 2019 - Mar 2020

Atlanta, GA, US

Full Stack Developer at Sideqik

I was working as full stack developer for a company and platform called Sideqik. We used to work with machine learning, big data, as well as data visualization and compelling user interfaces.

Technology stack: Ruby on Rails, Ember, ElasticSearch, PostgreSQL and MongoDB.

Website:

• https://sideqik.com/

Aug 2017 – Dec 2019

Tallinn, Estonia

Full Stack Developer at Mashta

I was a software developer at this outsourcing company. We were mainly working with MeteorJS, Node, ML, AI, mobile apps and MongoDB.

I developed an entire mobile client for Swedish company mobile app, using MeteorJS, Cordova, and BlazeJS.

I developed another app for an US start up from NY, called CliqUps. Used: MeteorJS, Cordova, React, etc..

Technology stack: Node.js, MeteorJS, Express, MongoDB, React, Blaze Cordova, Electron.

Website:

• https://www.nodepole.com/

Jan 2017 – Aug 2017

Tallinn, Estonia

Full Stack Developer at Zamphyr

I was working in the start up called Zamphyr.

Worked with MeteorJS, Node.js, BlazeJS, Microservices, DevOps, MongoDB, etc..

In the meantime I was working in the company called Microwork. I was making a worker app for company employees to collect data for Machine Learning and AI. Used: MeteorJS, Node.js, Blaze, CoffeeScript, MongoDB...

Websites:

- https://microwork.io/
- https://zamphyr.com/

Skills

EmberJS

Express.JS

Meteor.js

Ruby on Rails

• • • • • • • • •

• • • • • • • • •

ReactIS

PostgreSQL

MongoDB

Nov 2012 - Aug 2016

Web Developer at PopArtStudio

Novi Sad, Serbia

The first company that I've worked. Outsourcing company based on Technologies PHP, WordPress, SEO. Worked on several project as web dev.

Websites:

- https://megaplast.rs/
- https://aska.rs/

Sep 2012 - Dec 2016

Web Developer at Freelancing

Sarajevo, Bosnia and Novi Sad, Serbia

I started my career in web development as freelancer. I was working with PHP at that time and I was building different websites for different customers.

The main technologies used at that time are: PHP, CSS, Wordpress, Drupal, SEO optimization, MySQL...

Education

Oct 2018

Novi Sad, Serbia

Professional Bachelor in Electrical and Computer Engineering Faculty of Technical Science

P.B.El.Comp.Eng.

Jun 2015

High School, Gymnasium

Pale, Bosnia and Herzegovina

Awards

 Won the competition called CMBEBIH2019 in Banjaluka. Created a diagnostic support software based on the selected algorithm for the purpose of evolution of secondary amenorrhea diagnosis. Used ElectronJS and ReactJS Banjaluka/May 2019

https://cmbebih.com/

- Was a mentor for UN Open Data competition in Kikinda / April 2019
- Was in final of Metropolitan University competition. Made a website with PHP / 2014

Other projects

 Created an app for UNDP called Koshnica. Koshnica is open source platform with migration data from Serbia and Kikinda, Used data from https://data.gov.rs/sr/.

Technology stack: MeteorJS and subzero.cloud

https://kosnica.ktz.rs/

References

- Jeremy Haile / CEO of Sideqik jeremy@sideqik.com
- Marko Kažić / CEO of Zamphyr me@marxo.me